{
  "1": [
    {
      "question": "There is _____ * on the table .",
      "correctAnswer": "one",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["oen", "on"],
      "endOfQuestion": ["apple", "orange", "pear", "cucumber", "sandwich", "tomato", "potato", "lemon", "carrot", "banana", "cake", "biscuit", "computer", "phone"]
    },
    {
      "question": "There is _____ * on the chair .",
      "correctAnswer": "one",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["oen", "on"],
      "endOfQuestion": ["robot", "doll", "teddy", "clown", "skirt", "T-shirt", "sock", "umbrella", "glove", "hat", "jacket", "shoe", "scarf"]
    },
    {
      "question": "I have _____ * .",
      "correctAnswer": "one",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["oen", "on"],
      "endOfQuestion": ["apple", "orange", "pear", "cucumber", "sandwich", "tomato", "potato", "lemon", "carrot", "banana", "cake", "biscuit", "computer", "phone", "robot", "doll", "teddy", "clown", "skirt", "T-shirt", "sock", "umbrella", "glove", "hat", "jacket", "shoe", "scarf"]
    },
    {
      "question": "She has _____ * .",
      "correctAnswer": "one",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["oen", "on"],
      "endOfQuestion": ["apple", "orange", "pear", "cucumber", "sandwich", "tomato", "potato", "lemon", "carrot", "banana", "cake", "biscuit", "computer", "phone", "robot", "doll", "teddy", "clown", "skirt", "T-shirt", "sock", "umbrella", "glove", "hat", "jacket", "shoe", "scarf"]
    },
    {
      "question": "There is _____ * in the sky .",
      "correctAnswer": "one",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["oen", "on"],
      "endOfQuestion": ["moon", "sun", "cloud"]
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ * on the table .",
      "correctAnswer": "two",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["tow", "too"],
      "endOfQuestion": ["apples", "oranges", "pears", "cucumbers", "sandwiches", "tomatoes", "potatoes", "lemons", "carrots", "bananas", "cakes", "biscuits"]
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ * in the kitchen .",
      "correctAnswer": "three",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["tree", "thre"],
      "endOfQuestion": ["apples", "oranges", "pears", "cucumbers", "sandwiches", "tomatoes", "potatoes", "lemons", "carrots", "bananas", "cakes", "biscuits"]
    },
    {
      "question": "He has _____ * .",
      "correctAnswer": "four",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["foor", "phour"],
      "endOfQuestion": ["apples", "oranges", "pears", "cucumbers", "sandwiches", "tomatoes", "potatoes", "lemons", "carrots", "bananas", "cakes", "biscuits", "T-shirts", "socks", "hats", "jackets", "shorts", "trousers", "toys", "cars", "gloves"]
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ * in the bedroom .",
      "correctAnswer": "five",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["fife", "faiv"],
      "endOfQuestion": ["T-shirts", "socks", "hats", "jackets", "shorts", "trousers", "toys", "cars", "gloves"]
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ * .",
      "correctAnswer": "six",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["siks", "sixs"],
      "endOfQuestion": ["children", "boys", "girls", "men", "women", "animals", "cats", "apples", "oranges", "pears", "cucumbers", "sandwiches", "tomatoes", "potatoes", "lemons", "carrots", "bananas", "cakes", "biscuits", "dogs", "hamsters", "rabbits", "stars", "planes", "cars", "buses", "trains", "bikes", "boats", "tickets", "T-shirts", "socks", "hats", "jackets", "shorts", "trousers"]
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ * in the basket .",
      "correctAnswer": "seven",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["saven", "sevin"],
      "endOfQuestion": ["apples", "oranges", "pears", "cucumbers", "sandwiches", "tomatoes", "potatoes", "lemons", "carrots", "bananas", "cakes", "biscuits"]
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ books .",
      "correctAnswer": "eight",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["aight", "eigt"],
      "endOfQuestion": []
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ books .",
      "correctAnswer": "nine",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["nain", "ninee"],
      "endOfQuestion": []
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ books .",
      "correctAnswer": "ten",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["tan", "tene"],
      "endOfQuestion": []
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ books .",
      "correctAnswer": "eleven",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["ilevin", "elevene"],
      "endOfQuestion": []
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ books .",
      "correctAnswer": "twelve",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["twelf", "twelv"],
      "endOfQuestion": []
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ books .",
      "correctAnswer": "thirteen",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["thiteen", "thirtene"],
      "endOfQuestion": []
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ books .",
      "correctAnswer": "fourteen",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["foorteen", "fouteen"],
      "endOfQuestion": []
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ books .",
      "correctAnswer": "fifteen",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["fivteen", "fiveteen"],
      "endOfQuestion": []
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ books .",
      "correctAnswer": "sixteen",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["siksteen", "sixtene"],
      "endOfQuestion": []
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ books .",
      "correctAnswer": "seventeen",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["sevinteen", "seventene"],
      "endOfQuestion": []
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ books .",
      "correctAnswer": "eighteen",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["eigteen", "aighteen"],
      "endOfQuestion": []
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ books .",
      "correctAnswer": "nineteen",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["ninteen", "ninetene"],
      "endOfQuestion": []
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ books .",
      "correctAnswer": "twenty",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["tventy", "twente"],
      "endOfQuestion": []
    }
  ],
  "2": [
    {
      "question": "There are _____ # * on the table .",
      "correctAnswer": ["two", "three", "four", "five", "six", "seven", "eight", "nine", "ten", "eleven", "twelve", "thirteen", "fourteen", "fifteen", "sixteen", "seventeen", "eighteen", "nineteen", "twenty"],
      "incorrectAnswers": [],
      "endOfQuestion": ["apples", "oranges", "pears", "cucumbers", "sandwiches", "tomatoes", "potatoes", "lemons", "carrots", "bananas", "cakes", "biscuits"]
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ # * in the kitchen .",
      "correctAnswer": ["two", "three", "four", "five", "six", "seven", "eight", "nine", "ten", "eleven", "twelve", "thirteen", "fourteen", "fifteen", "sixteen", "seventeen", "eighteen", "nineteen", "twenty"],
      "incorrectAnswers": [],
      "endOfQuestion": ["apples", "oranges", "pears", "cucumbers", "sandwiches", "tomatoes", "potatoes", "lemons", "carrots", "bananas", "cakes", "biscuits"]
    },
    {
      "question": "He has _____ # *  .",
      "correctAnswer": ["two", "three", "four", "five", "six", "seven", "eight", "nine", "ten", "eleven", "twelve", "thirteen", "fourteen", "fifteen", "sixteen", "seventeen", "eighteen", "nineteen", "twenty"],
      "incorrectAnswers": [],
      "endOfQuestion": ["apples", "oranges", "pears", "cucumbers", "sandwiches", "tomatoes", "potatoes", "lemons", "carrots", "bananas", "cakes", "biscuits", "T-shirts", "socks", "hats", "jackets", "shorts", "trousers", "toys", "cars", "gloves"]
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ # * in the bedroom .",
      "correctAnswer": ["two", "three", "four", "five", "six", "seven", "eight", "nine", "ten", "eleven", "twelve", "thirteen", "fourteen", "fifteen", "sixteen", "seventeen", "eighteen", "nineteen", "twenty"],
      "incorrectAnswers": [],
      "endOfQuestion": ["T-shirts", "socks", "hats", "jackets", "shorts", "trousers", "toys", "cars", "gloves"]
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ # *  .",
      "correctAnswer": ["two", "three", "four", "five", "six", "seven", "eight", "nine", "ten", "eleven", "twelve", "thirteen", "fourteen", "fifteen", "sixteen", "seventeen", "eighteen", "nineteen", "twenty"],
      "incorrectAnswers": [],
      "endOfQuestion": ["apples", "oranges", "pears", "cucumbers", "sandwiches", "tomatoes", "potatoes", "lemons", "carrots", "bananas", "cakes", "biscuits", "T-shirts", "socks", "hats", "jackets", "shorts", "trousers", "toys", "cars", "gloves"]
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ # * in the basket .",
      "correctAnswer": ["two", "three", "four", "five", "six", "seven", "eight", "nine", "ten", "eleven", "twelve", "thirteen", "fourteen", "fifteen", "sixteen", "seventeen", "eighteen", "nineteen", "twenty"],
      "incorrectAnswers": [],
      "endOfQuestion": ["apples", "oranges", "pears", "cucumbers", "sandwiches", "tomatoes", "potatoes", "lemons", "carrots", "bananas", "cakes", "biscuits"]
    },
    {
      "question": "There are _____ # books .",
      "correctAnswer": ["two", "three", "four", "five", "six", "seven", "eight", "nine", "ten", "eleven", "twelve", "thirteen", "fourteen", "fifteen", "sixteen", "seventeen", "eighteen", "nineteen", "twenty"],
      "incorrectAnswers": [],
      "endOfQuestion": []
    }
  ]
}